
export const data = [
    {
        question: "In MS-Word, the number above the base-line is called",
        option1: "superscript",
        option2: "strike-through",
        option3: "subscript",
        option4: "above Baseline",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a window application",
        option1: "Notepad",
        option2: "Calculator",
        option3: "Wordpad",
        option4: "Tweetbot",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the full form of TCP?",
        option1: "Transmission Central Protocol",
        option2: "Transportation Control Protocol",
        option3: "Transport Control Protocol",
        option4: "Transmission Control Protocol",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "MS Word is an example of?",
        option1: "An Operating System",
        option2: "A processing device",
        option3: "Application Software",
        option4: "An input device",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is smallest unit of the information?",
        option1: "A bit",
        option2: "A byte",
        option3: "A block",
        option4: "A nibble",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the decimal equivalent of the binary number 10111?",
        option1: "21",
        option2: "39",
        option3: "42",
        option4: "23",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How many color dots make up one color pixel on a screen?",
        option1: "265",
        option2: "16",
        option3: "8",
        option4: "3",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How is the data stored on the diskette?",
        option1: "Ink",
        option2: "Laser bubbles",
        option3: "Magnetism",
        option4: "Circuits",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the smallest visual element on a video monitor?",
        option1: "Character",
        option2: "Pixel",
        option3: "Byte",
        option4: "Bit",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following natural element is the primary element in computer chips?",
        option1: "Silicon",
        option2: "Carbon",
        option3: "Iron",
        option4: "Uranium",
        ans: 1,
    },
]